hua hai hua hai
hua hai
[music]
Hello friends, a very warm welcome to
all of you on my YouTube channel, I am your
life insurance customer Kajal, in this video
we will talk about India's best
senior citizen subscribe, but
before starting I would like to request all of you to
please
subscribe, like my video and
definitely
subscribe, so
let's start today's meeting,
friends, let's learn
about some of the best senior citizen health insurance policies of popular insurance companies,
along with this, you will also learn about
buying a senior citizen health insurance policy, I will tell you about the benefits of a senior citizen health insurance
policy, do
not subscribe to this channel for senior citizens
and as the age increases, their
health deteriorates, which starts to deteriorate,
a senior citizen's corporation is limited, that is
why Umesh Jain, in such a situation, it becomes
very difficult for them to invest in funds for hospitalization and treatment expenses,
but it is in the evening
when a reliable senior citizen's health
insurance policy is for protection, you can now buy many
senior citizen health insurance policies
While buying an insurance policy, people hesitate thinking that
festival and health insurance
come with a premium and there are some benefits, but
this is not true. There are many senior
citizen insurance plans in the market which offer these and these can be
purchased. Friends, this is something that you can know.
Subscribe
Subscribe 1
Question Firstly,
Bajaj Allianz General Insurance Company can
take this cover for people aged 40-70 years. If we
talk about life insurance options, then from Rs. 50,000
Subscribe Subscribe Subscribe Subscribe Subscribe Subscribe Subscribe Subscribe Subscribe Subscribe Subscribe Subscribe Subscribe Subscribe Subscribe Subscribe Subscribe Subscribe Subscribe Subscribe Subscribe Subscribe Subscribe Subscribe Subscribe Subscribe Subscribe Subscribe Subscribe Subscribe Subscribe Subscribe Subscribe Subscribe Subscribe Subscribe Subscribe Subscribe Subscribe Subscribe Subscribe Subscribe Subscribe Subscribe Subscribe Subscribe Subscribe Subscribe Subscribe Subscribe Subscribe Subscribe Subscribe Subscribe Subscribe Subscribe Subscribe Subscribe Subscribe Subscribe Subscribe Subscribe Subscribe Subscribe Subscribe Subscribe Subscribe Subscribe Subscribe Subscribe Subscribe  Two
benefits can be purchased simultaneously and on the other hand,
you can subscribe at a table premium.
This is a line
hospitalization
subscription. If this is a
protection plan, then the general insurance
company is offering you
this senior citizen subscription. You can
subscribe to four different gold plated subscriptions which cover different insurance plans.
See the common benefits offered under the policy.
Subscribe to Platinum and Virendra Kanwar.
People aged 65 years can
subscribe to this policy by
taking ₹5
option. You can select this
subscription
[music]
so that you can set it for extra cost and
directly buy these special power secure.
Senior Citizen Health Insurance
Policy helps the older generation
to deal with health related problems
whose treatment cost is quite high.
Such conditions not only benefit the senior citizens
but also maintain good health. We will
talk about some benefits which we will discuss
soon and you should definitely buy
Senior Citizen Health Insurance
Policy. You can avail this policy without any extra cost.
This policy can increase the health of the person for a
long period. It is God's
creation.  Senior Citizen
Health Insurance
plans are designed to provide financial assistance to individuals above 60 years of age
for medical treatment, which is when they need it the most. Now, I will share some common features of senior citizen health insurance plans. Senior Citizen Health Insurance plans for individuals and
families can be purchased on a floater basis.
Most senior citizens do not require a pre-
medical screen in a health insurance plan.
These plans
offer a free look period to the policy buyer
during which they should thoroughly read and understand the terms and conditions of the policy.
Senior
citizens can avail
cashless high-quality treatment at network hospitals with the plan.
These
plans include room rent, doctor's office, medical
bills, and expenses covered. Senior Citizen
Health Insurance Plans Under Income Tax Act
If you don't have a festival, then
I will tell you that you should subscribe for the senior citizens living in your house.
Hello friends, before you buy any senior citizen
insurance product, make
sure that you check some factors
which will help you in taking the right decision. First,
know about it.
What you need to check is the cost.
You should look for a policy which is
designed for people with a mixed limited income. Secondly, look for Shirdi health
insurance plans which have
maximum features so that senior citizens can
easily get treatment. Coverage is a
policy which comes with old age. There are
some things to keep in mind while buying health insurance.
When you are ready to buy the
best health insurance policy for senior citizens in India, then take
a look at the key aspects that are being promoted before buying the policy. The
first one is the H factor. You should definitely subscribe to the policy of
a high definition company designed for senior citizens.
Some policies allow renewal till the age of 80
and some companies do not allow renewal till the age of 80.  The coverage of the policy will determine its
usefulness for senior citizens. You should
look for a
policy that covers medical coverage like labs, hypertension, pre-existing medical
coverage, and free medical plans so that in case of an emergency, senior citizens can get treatment without worrying. A 25% factor is the road hospital network. It
is important for senior citizens to buy a policy from a health insurance company that has a cashless
network. There is a large list of hospitals available for treatment without worrying about
last-minute hospitalizations.
Payment
Serials: Many insurance policies require you to
check the terms and conditions for
medical expenses.
Remember to check the terms and conditions for payment as
this also
sets the total amount to be paid by the bank.  Regarding the cream, the
policy of senior citizens is
very high. Companies
charge more in case of senior citizens
because they are more likely to suffer from diseases and ailments.
You should already know about the insurance. To
stay connected with us, the
policy holder
must get admitted in a hospital listed with the company.
Subscribe to the concerned company as soon as possible about the hospital admission.
By
subscribing, you can get treatment without any hassle
because the treatment expenses will be borne by the hospital
company. You will not have to pay any
bill. If you get admitted in a no-network
hospital and
want to get treatment in any other hospital, then
you just have to pay for it. So, how will you do it?
Check number one. Do inform the Vishwas provider about your hospital admission.
Avail the treatment benefits and
present this bill. Then register under the channel.
Subscribe to your Vishwas providers with doctor's prescription, hospital reports, chemist's bills, pathological reports. Subscribe to the
channel for
more information.  Click to verify
and if you get an improvement then
what all do
you need for claim settlement like medical report,
subscription is filled in your bank account, apart from this there is
subscription too, so friends this was a little
information about India's best senior
citizen health insurance policy, to
know more details about health and life insurance you
can contact me, you can
check it with the help of the number shown on the screen, so
friends this is all about today's video, the
information given in this video is
important information related to life for you,
we also want to talk to all of you,
for your continuous contribution subscribe to our channel, all the
people who are connected
with us
and if you subscribe to my channel
and you have liked
this video of ours, it has been very good